M Venkat Charan

Hyderabad, Telangana, India



mvcharan7009@gmail.com



9030393909



linkedin.com/in/urstrulyvc

Summary

Passion and ettiqute makes me to learn, adapt, and put all the experience to work. Upon being a student I feel that I am a bit forward in experiencing and analysing the needs and trends in present and changing social world. Working on real time business needs at different positions made my career challenging, and exploring different fields of work has become a hobby. Admiring to do master's from one of the world's best B-Schools in the fields of Operations management and IT can be stated as a reason to choose the different roles as an intern to gain the knowledge of a particular field.

I am an enthusiast in this modern changing world, tending to know and put my all efforts to bring the best output in every field or work that I choose.

Experience



Human Resources Intern

Griffon Technology: A Placement Partner Sep 2022 - Present (3 months +)

Marketing Intern

GoodSpace Aug 2022 - Oct 2022 (3 months)

Business Development Intern

ScarBluu Aug 2022 - Sep 2022 (2 months)

Education



Department of Commerce, Manipal Academy of Higher Education.

Bachelor of Business Administration - BBA, Business Administration and Management, General Aug 2021 - May 2024 **CGPA 8.0**

🔊 Narayana Junior College - India

Pre University 2019 - 2021 76.2%

Ramadevi public school

High School 2008 - 2019 80%

Licenses & Certifications

Macro economics - Coursera

SOCIAL MEDIA MARKETING - Coursera

Creative Problem Solving - Coursera
R98VMKQPGCYN

Skills

HR Management • Teamwork • Microsoft Office • Sourcing • Microsoft Excel • Negotiation • Corporate Communications • Marketing • Lead Generation • Business Development